GitHub - https://github.com/LiamMcBride

Personal Profile

Undergraduate, Sophomore at Virginia Tech pursuing Computer Science. Passionate about programming and software development. Previously experience with game design using C#, Unity, and Blender. Currently focused on projects in Java, Python, and utilizing APIs. Personable and gets along with peers. Always learning more and pursuing multiple interests.

Experience

Paid Internship at Ubisoft (05/2019 - 08/2019)

Customer support agent dealing with fraud detection, account verification, and other customer issues.

Black Falcons (Ubuntu and Cisco Packet Tracer Specialist, 05/2018 - 05/2020)

Cyber Patriots highschool club hosted by the Airforce. Deals with cybersecurity and advanced IT work. Was a team lead. Team's Ubuntu and Networking expert. Placed 2nd at state level.

Pizza Hut Driver (05/2020 - 07/2020)

Delivery driver along with janitorial and food prep work.

Exelaration Software Engineer Intern (09/2021 - Current)

Working as a consultant for <u>Rhythm</u>'s Customer Support portal. Utilizing Django, React, Typescript, and Docker to perform end-to-end modifications on the existing system.

Education

Undergraduate at Virginia Tech(08/2020 - Current)

Class of 2024. Computer Science Major.

Cisco Networking Academy Packet Tracer(2019)

In-depth configuration of LAN networks.

Unity Envision course at George Mason University(07/2018)

College-level course on Game Design, Unity, and C#.

Skills

Languages

C#, Python, Java, JavaScript, and TypeScript.

Tools and Frameworks

Unity, Blender, Git, Django, React, and Docker.

Linux

Ubuntu

Activities

Cross Country and Track(2014 - 2020)

Liam McBride

205 Benwell Ct. - Cary, NC 27519 801-231-5038 - <u>mailmcbride@vt.edu</u> GitHub - <u>https://github.com/LiamMcBride</u>

4 Year varsity runner as well as team captain.